http://www.collegetoolkit.com/terms-privacy-disclaimer/#interest-based-ads

Registered-User and Website Visitor Conduct
Liability for Technical Disruptions to Our Website(s)
1. Accepting Edvisors’ Terms of Use
Edvisors Network, Inc. (“Edvisors,” “ENI,” “we,” “us,” “our”), a Massachusetts corporation, operates several websites, including but not limited to the following:
Edvisors.com
ScholarshipPoints.om
PrivateStudentLoans.com
HowToGetIn.com
RewardFish.com
StudentLoanConsolidator.com
FinancialAidForum.com
CollegeToolkit.com
StudentScholarshipSearch.com
Edvisors provides its services to you through its Websites (“Website”), mobile applications and related services, including, but not limited to, the RewardFish® program (collectively, “Services”), subject to the following Terms of Use. By accessing this Website, mobile application or using the Services, you agree to these Terms of Use. If you do not agree to any of the terms and conditions of these Terms of Use, please do not use the Services and exit the website now. You may be required to register with Edvisors in order to access and use certain Services or features (“Registered Services”). If you choose to register, you must meet the eligibility requirements of the website and your choice to register for such Registered Services indicates your acceptance of these Terms of Use.
2. Privacy Policy
As a condition for using the Service(s), you agree that you have read, understood and accept Edvisors’ Privacy Policy, which may be updated from time to time. After notice of a change to the privacy policy, continued use of the website(s) will be deemed acceptance of the policy.
3. Changes to Edvisors’ Terms of Use and Our Services
We reserve the right to modify these Terms of Use at any time and in our sole discretion without prior notice. Furthermore, we reserve the right to add to, update, delete from or modify the Services at any time and in our sole discretion. We may post or display notices of changes to the Term of Use on or through the Services. Once posted, these changes to the Terms of Use become effective immediately. If any change that we make is not acceptable to you, your sole recourse shall be to cease using the Services. Any access or use by you of the Services after any changes to our Terms of Use constitutes conclusive evidence of your acknowledgement of the modification to these Terms of Use and your agreement to be bound by such change(s). You should check back regularly and review these Terms of Use. Any new or additional feature of the Services shall be subject to these Terms of Use.
4. Third-Party Links and Content
Edvisors does not exercise editorial control over third-party content provided, uploaded, published, or distributed by users and other participants on Edvisors websites. In other words, the Edvisors website(s) is/are merely a distributor, not a publisher, of such content. Such content may contain the views, opinions, statements, offers, and other material of the respective users, suppliers, participants, or authors. Edvisors does not endorse, is not responsible for, and makes no representations or warranties regarding, such content or its accuracy, supplier ability or fitness for any particular purpose, and Edvisors shall not be liable for any harm resulting from or in connection with reliance on any such content, including, but not limited to, claims for defamation, libel, slander, infringement, invasion of privacy and publicity rights, obscenity, pornography, profanity, fraud, or misrepresentation. In addition, the Edvisors. shall not be a party to or liable in any way for any harm associated with, any transaction between our users and any other user or participant on the website(s). Notwithstanding the foregoing, Edvisors reserves the right to block or remove communications, postings or materials at any time in our sole discretion.
The Services may contain links to third-party websites or applications that are not owned or controlled by Edvisors. Edvisors has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for the products, services, content, privacy policies or practices of any third-party website or application. In addition, Edvisors is unable and unwilling to censor or edit the content of any third-party website or application. By accessing and using the Services, you expressly relieve Edvisors from any and all liability arising from your use of any linked third-party website or application.
Accordingly, we encourage you to be aware when you leave our Services and to read the terms and conditions and privacy policy of each website or application that you access or use. If you decide to access any other websites or applications linked to or from our Services, you do so entirely at your own risk. Any questions, complaints, or claims related to any product or service provided by a third-party on the Services should be directed to the applicable third-party.
The Services display some content which is not Edvisors’. This content is the sole responsibility of the individual or entity that makes the content available.
5. User Submissions and User Responsibilities
The Services may permit the submission of certain user-generated text, information, data, video, chats, audio, photographs, files, messages or other content to or through the Services (“User Submissions”) and the hosting, sharing, transmission and/or publishing (“posting”) of such User Submissions. User Submissions may be used, distributed and published by Edvisors and viewed by both general users and Members of the Services. You understand that Edvisors does not guarantee any confidentiality with respect to any User Submissions.
Edvisors encourages you to carefully choose the information you submit, post, or provide to others using the Services or Services features (including, but not limited to, comments, blogs, video chat sessions, mobile application, Promotions entries, or Contest entries). Edvisors does not endorse any User Submission or any opinion, recommendation, or advice expressed therein. Any conversations or information you have or share with others using features that are available on the Services and any User Submissions may be accessible and viewable by all other users or by other Members of the Services. Edvisors reserves the right, but undertakes no duty, to remove, edit, or reject any User Submissions at any time, in its sole discretion, for any reason or no reason, including User Submissions that in the sole judgment of Edvisors violate these Terms of Use, or which might be offensive, illegal, or that might violate the rights, harm, or threaten the safety of users or others. Even after a User Submission is removed from the Services, whether such removal or deletion is by you or by us, copies of that User Submission
may be retained and/or remain viewable by us, our licensors, vendors, service providers and/or other third parties, including other users. Edvisors may restrict, suspend or terminate any user’s access to or use of all or any part of the Services or its features at any time, for any reason, with or without notice and with no liability to Edvisors whatsoever.
You shall be solely responsible for your own User Submissions and the consequences of posting them and you agree that we are only acting as a passive conduit for your online distribution and publication of your User Submissions.  In connection with User Submissions, you affirm, represent and warrant that: (i) you own or have the necessary licenses, rights, consents and permissions to use and authorize Edvisors to use all copyrights, trademarks, trade secrets, patents or any other proprietary or personal rights in and to your User Submissions to enable inclusion and use of such User Submissions in the manner contemplated by the Services and their Terms of Use; (ii) posting your User Submission on or through the Services does not and will not violate any confidentiality obligations between you and any person or organization or the privacy rights, publicity rights or other rights of any person; and (iii) you have the written consent, release and/or permission of each and every identifiable person or organization in your User Submission to use the name or likeness of each and every such identifiable person or organization to enable inclusion and use of the User Submissions in the manner contemplated by the Services and these Terms of Use. You further affirm, represent and warrant that your User Submissions are not defamatory or libelous in any manner whatsoever. Edvisors reserves the right to remove user submission(s).
You shall be solely responsible for your own User Submissions and the consequences of posting them and you agree that we are only acting as a passive conduit for your online distribution and publication of your User Submissions.
In connection with User Submissions, you affirm, represent and warrant that: (i) you own or have the necessary licenses, rights, consents and permissions to use and authorize Edvisors to use all copyrights, trademarks, trade secrets, patents or any other proprietary or personal rights in and to your User Submissions to enable inclusion and use of such User Submissions in the manner contemplated by the Services and their Terms of Use; (ii) posting your User Submission on or through the Services does not and will not violate any confidentiality obligations between you and any person or organization or the privacy rights, publicity rights or other rights of any person; and (iii) you have the written consent, release and/or permission of each and every identifiable person or organization in your User Submission to use the name or likeness of each and every such identifiable person or organization to enable inclusion and use of the User Submissions in the manner contemplated by the Services and these Terms of Use. You further affirm, represent and warrant that your User Submissions are not defamatory or libelous in any manner whatsoever. Edvisors reserves the right to remove user submission(s).
User agrees to indemnify Edvisors for any content User post which user does not have the requisite permission as affirmed in (i) - (iii) in the foregoing paragraph.
You are solely responsible at your sole cost and expense for creating backup copies and replacing any User Submission you post or store through the Services or provide to Edvisors.
All User Submissions posted on Edvisors’ Websites or through Edvisors’ Services will be the exclusive property of Edvisors.
Some areas of the Websites allow Users to post content such as comments, questions, and other content or information (“User-Generated Content”).
We may moderate the comments that appear on our Websites.
We reserve the right but do not assume the obligation to delete or withhold publication of comments that violate our standards. Comments that are obscene, libelous or defamatory, or include vicious personal attacks will not be published. Comments or images that are racist, sexist, homophobic or otherwise offensive will not be published.
Additionally, you agree not to engage in any of the following prohibited activities or behaviors:
impersonate, imitate or pretend to be somebody else, by setting up different accounts/profiles, or falsely state, represent, or imply any affiliation, association, or connection with a person or entity when using the Websites;
post, upload, transmit, send or otherwise make available on or through the Websites any content that constitutes junk mail, spam, pyramid schemes, chain letters, phishing, advertising, and/or commercial offers;
use any language that is, or post, upload, transmit, send or otherwise make available on or through the Websites any User-Generated Content about a person or group that is violent or that victimizes, degrades, defiles or disparages any person or group based on race, color, religion, national origin, ancestry, citizenship status, physical or mental disability, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity and expression, age, medical condition, or veteran status or otherwise engage in what we deem to be racism, sexism, ageism, religious intolerance, bigotry, ethnic slurs, or homophobia;
use any language, or post, upload, transmit, send or otherwise make available on or through the Websites any User-Generated Content that may or is intended to enable, authorize, instruct, encourage, assist, suggest, or promote activities that incite violence, constitute a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability, or otherwise violate any local, state, federal, provincial, national, international, or foreign law, rule or regulation, including without limitation libel, child pornography, fraud, or invasion of privacy;
stalk others on or through the Websites, or using information obtained on or through the Websites;
disrupt, overwhelm, attack, hack, destroy, damage, disable, impair, repossess, alter, tamper or interfere with the Websites, including without limitation any content, communications, messaging, programming, hardware, functionality, or features on our networks, servers or databases, or impede or interfere with others' access, visitation, and/or use of the Websites, in any way or by any means, whether remotely or by access to our personal property, premises, or otherwise, including, without limitation, by using administrator passwords or by masquerading as an administrator while using the Websites or otherwise;
post, upload, transmit, send or otherwise make available on or through the Websites any software disabling devices, time bombs, Trojan horses, cancelbots, viruses, worms, bugs, corrupted files, spyware, adware, malware, malicious programs or code, or devices or defects of similar nature;
disseminate or transmit any Content that infringes or violates any party's copyright, trademark, trade secret, patent or other proprietary right; or use or distribute third-party information (whether or not protected as a trade secret) in violation of a duty of confidentiality, fiduciary duty, or similar duty;
violate any law (whether local, state, national, or international), whether or not intentionally;
forge headers or otherwise intentionally disguise the origin of any content or communication; interfere with or disrupt the Sites, or servers or networks connected to the Sites; or disobey any requirements, procedures, policies, or regulations of networks connected to the Sites;
"Frame" or "mirror" any part of the Sites; or
engage in any other activity deemed by Edvisors to be in conflict with the spirit or intent of this agreement or that might violate the rights of others or give rise to liability.
You understand that by using the Sites, you may be exposed to Content that may offend you or challenge your beliefs. Your remedy is to avoid such Content by discontinuing your access.
Website Activity Analysis
We may analyze activity on the Websites to foster compliance with the Terms of Use. You hereby specifically agree to such analysis. Nevertheless, we do not make any representations, warranties or guarantees that: (1) the Websites, or any portion thereof, will in fact be analyzed for any particular purpose(s), (2) apparent statements of fact not made by Edvisors will be authenticated or substantiated, or (3) we will take any specific action (or any action at all) in the event of a challenge or dispute regarding compliance or non-compliance with the Terms of Use.
6. Digital Millennium Copyright Act
Edvisors responds to notices of alleged copyright infringement and terminates accounts of repeat infringers according to the process set out in the DMCA (see 17 U.S.C. 512(c)(3) for further information). To file a notice of infringement you must provide a written communication that sets forth the items specified below. You may be liable for damages (including damages, costs, and attorneys’ fees) if you materially misrepresent that the Websites, a web page or any content on the Websites is infringing your copyright. As such, before submitting a DMCA notice, it’s important to consider if the manner in which the material is used falls under the doctrine of fair use. If you are not sure whether material located on a Edvisors site infringes your copyright, or if it is subject to fair use protections, you should first consider seeking legal advice.
A. Notification. If you are a copyright owner or an agent thereof and believe that any User Submission or other Edvisors content infringes upon your copyright, you may submit a written notification pursuant to the DMCA by providing our Copyright Agent (listed below) with the following information: (i) an electronic or physical signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that I allegedly infringed; (ii) a description of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed or if multiple copyrighted works are covered by the notification, a representative list of such works on or in the Services: (iii) a description of the location on the Services or Websites of the allegedly infringed material(s); (iv) your address, telephone number, and email address; (v) a written statement that you have a good faith belief that use of the material(s) in the matter complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and (vi) a written statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that you are authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
Edvisors’ designated Copyright Agent for notice of claims of infringement is:
Compliance Department
College Loan Corporation
10000 W. Charleston Blvd., Suite 200
Las Vegas, NV 89135
Email: DMCA@Edvisors.com
Telephone: (702) 777-8405
Only notices of alleged copyright infringement should go to the Copyright Agent; any other feedback, comments, requests for technical support, and other communications should be directed to Edvisors’ customer service at customerservice@edvisors.com. You acknowledge that if you fail to comply with all of the notice requirements of the DMCA, your notice may not be valid.
B. Termination of Repeat Offenders. In accordance with the DMCA and other applicable law, Edvisors shall, in appropriate circumstances, terminate access, at Edvisors’ sole discretion, of any general user or Member that Edvisors finds to be a repeat infringer of other copyrights. Edvisors may also, in its sole discretion, limit or fully terminate access to the Website or Service(s) of any user infringing the intellectual property rights of others, regardless of whether such user is a repeat offender or not.
7. Children’s Online Privacy Protection Notice
This Website is not directed or otherwise promoted for use by children under the age of thirteen (13). Edvisors does not knowingly collect, maintain or use personal information from our websites about children under age 13. If a child whom we know to be under age 13 sends personal information to us online, we will only use that information to respond directly to that child, notify parents or seek parental consent, and will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. We are not, however, responsible for the collection and use of information by companies or individuals unaffiliated with us whose websites may contain links to ours. Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, we also do not knowingly distribute such information to third-parties. We do not knowingly allow children under the age of 13 to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information via our site.
8. Proprietary Rights to Content
You agree that title, ownership rights, and other intellectual property and proprietary rights in the Services shall remain in Edvisors and/or its licensors and suppliers. You acknowledge that the content of this Website and the Services - including but not limited to text, sound, photographs, graphics, software or other material contained in either Edvisors, Sponsor, Client, Affiliate or Reward Partner electronic mail communications, services or software - is copyrighted by Edvisors and/or its licensors and suppliers under United States and international copyright laws, is subject to other intellectual property and proprietary rights and laws, and is owned by Edvisors or its licensors and suppliers. Such content may not be copied, modified, reproduced, republished, posted, transmitted, sold, offered for sale, or redistributed in any way without the prior written permission of Edvisors and its applicable licensors or suppliers, with the sole exception that one copy of any necessary software that may be provided by Edvisors, its Clients, Affiliates, Sponsors or Reward Partners may be downloaded onto a single computer for your personal, noncommercial use. You must abide by all copyright notices, information, or restrictions contained in or attached to any such content. You may use Edvisors’, Sponsor’s, Client’s, Affiliates or Reward Partners’ content, service or software only as expressly authorized by Edvisors, the Sponsor, the Client , the Affiliate or the Reward Partner.
You acknowledge and agree that the Services and any necessary software provided by Edvisors or its Sponsors, Clients, Affiliate, Reward Partners or other third-party partners and used in connection with the Services (“Software”) contain proprietary and confidential information that is protected by applicable intellectual property and other laws. Edvisors grants you a personal, nontransferable and nonexclusive right and license to use the object code of any such Software on a single computer and solely in connection with your use of this Website and the Services; provided that you do not (and do not allow any third-party to) otherwise copy, modify, create a derivative work of, reverse engineer, reverse assemble or otherwise attempt to discover any source code, sell, assign, rent, lease, loan, sublicense, grant a security interest in, or otherwise transfer any right in any such Software. You agree not to modify any such Software in any manner or form, or to use modified versions of any such Software, including (without limitation) for the purpose of obtaining unauthorized access to the Services. You agree not to access the Services by any means other than through the interface that is provided by Edvisors for such use.
9. Eligibility for Registered Services
Some Edvisors’ websites require registration in order to fully use the website. You will be required to register if you wish to obtain access to Edvisors Websites that provide Registered Services and become a registered member (“Member”), subject to the following eligibility requirements: (i) Members must be thirteen years or older at the time of registration; (ii) membership is limited to individuals only, corporations or other business entities may not become Members; (iii) Registered Services are limited to one account per individual, even if the individual has multiple email addresses; (iv) employees of Edvisors and members of their household are not eligible to participate; and (v) automated services, scripts, or other machines are not eligible. Some Registered Services have additional eligibility requirements, which will be contained within the specific terms and conditions of Member Agreements associated with participation in those Registered Services.
10. Registration and Site Visitation Obligations
To access and use Services, you need computer equipment and telecommunications access necessary to connect to and access the World Wide Web. You must provide, at your own expense, all equipment, all services (including, where applicable, telephone service) and all related third-party service fees such as ISP charges) necessary to access the Services and any future enhancements or additional services. In consideration of use of Registered Services, you agree to provide to Edvisors and its third-party partners true, accurate, current, and complete information as prompted by the Registered Service Website’s online registration form (the “Registration Data”) and agree to maintain and promptly update the Registration Data as necessary in order to keep it true, accurate, current, and complete. If you provide any information that is untrue, inaccurate, not current, or incomplete, Edvisors may suspend or terminate your account and/or access to the Website immediately and may refuse you all current or future use of the Registered Service. Some Services include Promotions and Contests. If you are the winner of any such Promotion or Contest you understand you may be required to allow Edvisors to use your name, likeness, testimonials, contest submissions and biographical information for future promotional material along with reporting required by law.
11. Registered Services Password and Account Access
Members of Registered Services have certain Rights & Responsibilities with respect to Password and Account Access: (i) Member must select a password as part of the registration process (unless the Member logs in using a third-party social media functionality such as Facebook Connect); (ii) in order to prevent unauthorized activity, to access the Registered Service on the Internet, Member must give the Registered Service their e-mail address and selected password in order to update Member profile information, update personal information (name, e-mail address, etc.) and participate in Promotions and Contests: (iii) for security purposes, Member is advised to memorize, and not to write down, his/her password; (iv) Member is responsible for keeping his/her e-mail address and password confidential, and is solely responsible for all activities that occur under Member’s e-mail address and password, including all unauthorized activities: (v) Member agrees to (a) immediately notify Edvisors of any unauthorized use of Member’s e-mail address and password or any other breach of security related to this Website or the Service, and (b) ensure that Member logs out from Member’s account at the end of each session; and (vi) Member agrees to abide by all applicable local, state, federal, and international laws and regulations with respect to Member’s account.
Edvisors has certain Rights & Responsibilities with respect to Password and Account Access: (i) Edvisors will implement security measures at or above industry standards to secure Member’s password on the database; (ii) Edvisors is entitled to act on instructions received under Member’s password and e-mail address; and (iii) Edvisors cannot and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from Member’s failure to adequately safeguard Member’s e-mail address and/or password.
12. Registered-User and Website Visitor Conduct
You agree not to use any website with Edvisors service marks, including but not limited to Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, blogs or other social media site, or this Website to: (i) violate any local, state, national or international law; (ii) stalk, harass, or harm another individual; (iii) collect or store personal data about other Website visitors or registered users; (iv) impersonate any person, or otherwise misrepresent your identity; (v) interfere with, disrupt or violate these Terms of Use and operating rules of the Services or servers or networks connected to the Services; or disobey any requirements, procedures, policies, or regulations of such networks; (vi) interfere with another Website visitor’s or registered user’s use of the Services; (vii) attempt to gain unauthorized access to the Services, or to other accounts, computer systems, or networks connected to the Services; (viii) transmit any file that contains viruses, worms, Trojan horses, or any other contaminating or destructive features; (ix) use the Services to conduct any activity or solicit the performance of any illegal activity or other activity that infringes the rights of others; (x) resell, barter, trade, auction or otherwise generate income by providing access to the Services to others; (xi) exploit bugs, coding or scripting error to achieve a task, participate in or rig a contest, sweepstakes or other activity.
You may not upload, post, email, transmit or otherwise make available any User Submission that infringes any patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright or other proprietary rights of any party.
You may not access the Service for purposes of monitoring its availability, performance or functionality, or for any other benchmarking or competitive purposes. Additionally, you may not use the Services in connection with affiliate programs, multi-level marketing schemes, sites/blogs, repurposing existing stories (source hops), or off-topic content.
You may not change, reorganize, modify, copy, reverse engineer, or create derivative works from the Services or any part thereof, in order to (i) build a competitive product or Service; (ii) build a product using similar ideas, features, functions, or graphics of the Service; (iii) remove, change or replace any Edvisors’ trademarks, logos, copyrights, or any other branding elements; (iv) hide, obscure, disable, or otherwise render inoperable any portion of the User interface including, but not limited to, the display of advertisements and promotions within the Services; or (v) copy any content, ideas, features, functions, or graphics of the Services. In addition, you may not use any meta tags or any other “hidden text” using Edvisors’ name or other trademark or service mark, nor any Edvisors logo or other proprietary graphic or service mark as part of a link, without the express written consent of Edvisors.
You may not use any “deep-link,” “page-scrape,” “robot,” “spider” or other automatic device, algorithm or methodology, or any similar or equivalent manual process, to access, acquire, copy or monitor any portion of the website and Services, or in any way reproduce or circumvent the navigational structure or presentation of the Services to obtain or attempt to obtain any materials, documents or information through any means not purposely made available through the Services. Additionally, you may not take any action that imposes, or may impose (as judged by Edvisors at its sole discretion) an unreasonable or disproportionately large load on our infrastructure.
You may not attempt to gain unauthorized access to any portion or feature of the Services, or any other systems or networks connected to the Services or to any Edvisors server, or to any of the services offered on or through the Services, by hacking, password “mining” or any other illegitimate means. You may not harvest or collect User names, User IDs, email addresses or any other User identifying information by electronic or other means for the purpose of sending unsolicited email or other communications. Unauthorized commercial advertisements, affiliate links, and other forms of solicitation may be removed from User profiles and/or community postings without notice and may result in termination of User privileges.
13. Liability for Technical Disruptions to Our Website(s)
If you cause a technical disruption of our website or any aspect of its functionality you agree to be responsible for any and all loss, costs, liabilities or expenses Edvisors may suffer and you agree to be liable for any attorneys' fees and costs arising from and/or related to the same. The foregoing shall be without limitation of our other venders in law or equity.
14. Disclaimer of Warranties
You agree that use of the Services and this Website is solely at your own risk. All Services offered by Edvisors are provided on a strictly “as is” and “as available” basis, without representation or warranty of any kind. Neither Edvisors nor its third-party partners make any warranty, express or implied: (i) with regard to any products, services, or gifts obtained by you through the Services or through any third-party; (ii) that the services will meet your requirements; (iii) that the Services will be uninterrupted, timely, free of errors or without defects; (iv) as to the results you may obtain by using the Services; (v) as to the accuracy or reliability of any information obtained via the Services; or tax liability imposed against you by any taxing authority.
TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PROVIDED BY APPLICABLE LAW, EDVISORS EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL EXPRESS, IMPLIED AND STATUTORY WARRANTIES REGARDING THE INFORMATION, SERVICES OR GOODS PROVIDED BY OR THROUGH THE SERVICES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO: (I) THE IMPLIED WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY; (II) THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USER OR PURPOSE; AND (III) NON-INFRINGEMENT. EDVISORS CANNOT AND SHALL NOT BE LIABLE OR RESPONSIBLE FOR THOSE GUARANTEES, WARRANTIES, AND REPRESENTATIONS, IF ANY, OFFERED BY ANY THIRD-PARTY INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO: CLIENTS, SPONSORS, REWARD PARTNERS, MANUFACTURERS OF MERCHANDISE OR SUPPLIERS OF SERVICES. NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY YOU FROM EDVISORS OR VIA THE SERVICES SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY NOT EXPRESSLY MADE HEREIN.To the extent that we may not, as a matter of applicable law, disclaim any implied warranty, the scope and duration of such warranty shall be the minimum permitted under such applicable law.
15. Limitation of Liability
You understand that some goods and services offered through the Services may be offered by third-parties or affiliates, and that Edvisors does not operate, control or endorse any of their information, goods or services in any way. You understand that third-parties may place restrictions on the use of goods and services offered through the Services. To the fullest extent provided by applicable law, neither Edvisors nor its officers, directors, stockholders, subsidiaries, employees, agents, licensors, affiliates, or other third-party providers shall be held liable for any damages or losses of any kind, whether direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential or exemplary damages resulting from: (i) the use or inability to use the Services; (ii) the cost of procurement of substitute goods or services; (iii) any transaction entered into or through the Services; (iv) the reliance on or use of any information, goods, services or merchandise provided through the Services; (v) unauthorized access to or alteration of your transmissions or data; (vi) statements or conduct of any third-party; (vii) any claim attributable to errors, omissions, or other inaccuracies in the Services and/or materials or information retrieved through the Services; (viii) any tax obligations arising from or related to your use of Edvisors Website or the Services or (ix) any other matter relating to the Services, your relationship with Edvisors or these Terms of Use.
The above limitation is applicable even if Edvisors or its authorized representatives have been advised of (or know or should know of) the possibility of such damages. Because some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of certain warranties or the limitation or exclusion of liability for certain types of damages, some of the above limitations and disclaimers may not apply to you. Your rights vary from jurisdiction to jurisdiction. You acknowledge and agree that Edvisors neither endorses the contents of any electronic mail or Internet communications sent by third-parties or affiliates nor shall be held responsible or liable for: (i) the accuracy of material contained in electronic mail, Internet, or other communications of third-parties or affiliates; (ii) any infringement of third-party intellectual property rights arising from the electronic mail Internet, or other communications from third-parties or affiliates; or (iii) any fraud or other crime facilitated by the electronic mail, Internet, or other communications by third-parties or affiliates. To the fullest extent provided by applicable law, you agree that Edvisors is not liable to you or to any third-party for any modification, suspension or discontinuances of services from particular providers to the Services.
16. Indemnification
YOU AGREE TO INDEMNIFY AND HOLD HARMLESS EDVISORS AND ITS SUBSIDIARIES, PREDECESSORS, SUCCESSORS, AFFILIATES, OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, LICENSORS, SUPPLIERS, CO-BRANDERS, THIRD-PARTY PROVIDERS, CLIENTS, SPONSORS, REWARD PARTNERS OR OTHER PARTNERS, FROM AND AGAINST ANY AND ALL CLAIMS, LOSSES, COSTS (INCLUDING COURT COSTS), FEES (INCLUDING ATTORNEY’S FEES), DAMAGES AND EXPENSES THAT SUCH PARTIES MAY INCUR AS A RESULT OF, DUE TO, OR ARISING OUT OF THE VIOLATION BY YOU (OR ANYONE ACTING UNDER YOU ACCOUNT OR PASSWORD) OF THESE TERMS OF USE,
THE USE OR MISUSE OF THE SERVICES BY YOU (OR ANYONE ACTING UNDER YOUR ACCOUNT OR PASSWORD), OR THE VIOLATION OF ANY RIGHTS OF ANOTHER BY YOU (OR ANYONE ACTING UNDER YOUR ACCOUNT OR PASSWORD).
17. Use and Storage
You acknowledge that Edvisors may establish general practices and limits concerning use of the Services including, without limitation, the maximum number of days that information, data, account history or other uploaded content will be retained by the Services, the maximum disk space that will be allotted on Edvisors servers on your behalf, and the maximum number of times (and the maximum duration for which) you may access the Services in a given period of time. You acknowledge that Edvisors reserves the right to terminate accounts that are inactive for an extended period of time, as determined by Edvisors in its sole discretion. You further acknowledge that Edvisors reserves the right to change these general practices and limits at any time, in its sole discretion, with or without notice. You agree that Edvisors has no responsibility or liability for the deletion or failure to store any information or data and other communications or other content maintained or transmitted by or through the Services.
18. Trademark Information
All Edvisors trademarks, as well as any third-party trademarks, service marks, logos and trade names appearing on this Website or on or through the Services, are the property of their respective owners, and you may not copy or use them in any manner.
Nothing contained on this Website should be understood as granting you a license to use any of the trademarks, service marks, or logos owned by Edvisors or by any third party.
19. Arbitration: PLEASE READ CAREFULLY. IT AFFECTS YOUR RIGHTS
A. Most of your concerns can be resolved quickly by contacting Edvisors at info@edvisors.com. In the event that we cannot resolve your concern, binding arbitration through the following procedures shall be your sole and exclusive remedy. Any arbitration under these Terms of Use will take place on an individual basis; class arbitrations and class actions are not permitted.
B. Pursuant to the Federal Arbitration Act, Edvisors and you agree to arbitrate all disputes and claims between us. This agreement to arbitrate is intended to be broadly interpreted. It includes, but is not limited to, claims arising out of or relating to any aspect of the relationship between us, regardless of legal theory, including, but not limited to, claims relating to advertising and claims relating to any and all use of the Service(s), whether brought during or after the term of these Terms of Use. References to “Edvisors,” “you,” and “us” include our respective corporate subsidiaries and parents, affiliates, agents, employees, officers, directors, predecessors in interest, successors, and assigns, as well as all authorized or unauthorized users or beneficiaries of services under these Terms of Use or prior agreements between us. Notwithstanding the foregoing, either party may bring an individual action in small claims court.
You agree that, by accepting these Terms of Use, you and Edvisors are each waiving the right to a trial by jury or to participate in a class action. This Section 19 shall survive termination of these Terms of Use.
C. A party who intends to seek arbitration must first send to the other, by certified mail, a written Notice of Dispute (“Notice”). The Notice to Edvisors shall be addressed to Edvisors Network, Inc., 10000 W. Charleston Blvd., Suite 200, Las Vegas, NV 89135, Attention: President (“Edvisors Notice Address”). The Notice to you shall be addressed to any such addresses, including email addresses you may have provided Edvisors. If you have never provided Edvisors with any such address, Edvisors will, after using due diligence to discover, send Notice to your last known mailing address. The Notice must (a) describe the nature and basis of the claim or dispute; and (b) set forth the specific relief sought (“Demand”). The Demand must be made within a reasonable time after a dispute has arisen, but in no event shall it be made more than one year from when the aggrieved party knew or should have known of the claim or facts forming the basis of the dispute. If Edvisors and you do not reach an agreement to resolve the claim informally within 30 days after the Notice is received, you or Edvisors may commence an arbitration proceeding. During the arbitration, the amount of any settlement offer made by Edvisors or you shall not be disclosed to the arbitrator until after the arbitrator determines the amount, if any, to which you or Edvisors is entitled.
D. The arbitration will be governed by the Commercial Arbitration Rules and the Supplementary Procedures for Consumer Related Disputes (collectively, “AAA Rules”) of the American Arbitration Association (“AAA”), as modified by this Agreement, and will be administered by the AAA. The arbitration will take place before a single arbitrator appointed in accordance with the AAA Rules. The arbitrator is bound by the terms of this Agreement and must issue a written decision sufficient to explain the essential findings and conclusions on which an award is based. All issues are for the arbitrator to decide, except that issues relating to the scope and enforceability of the arbitration provisions in this Section 19 are for a court to decide. Unless Edvisors and you agree otherwise, any arbitration hearings will take place in Clark County, Nevada. If your claim is for $10,000 or less, the arbitration will be conducted solely on the basis of documents submitted to the arbitrator unless otherwise directed by the AAA Rules. Each party will bear its own attorneys’ fees and costs. Arbitration fees will be allocated in accordance with the AAA Rules. Judgment on the award rendered by the arbitrator, if any, may be entered for enforcement purposes only in any court having jurisdiction thereof.
E. The arbitrator may award declaratory or injunctive relief only in favor of the individual party seeking relief and only to the extent necessary to provide relief warranted by that party’s individual claim. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, the arbitrator may not award declaratory or injunctive relief to the extent it affects conduct between a party and a non-party. YOU AND EDVISORS AGREE THAT EACH MAY BRING CLAIMS AGAINST THE OTHER ONLY IN YOUR OR ITS INDIVIDUAL CAPACITY AND NOT AS A PLAINTIFF OR CLASS MEMBER IN ANY PURPORTED CLASS OR REPRESENTATIVE PROCEEDING SUCH AS A CLASS ACTION, CLASS ARBITRATION OR MASS JOINDER PROCEEDING. Further, unless both you and Edvisors agree otherwise, the arbitrator may not consolidate more than one person’s claims, and may not otherwise preside over any form of a representative or class proceeding. If this class action waiver is found to be unenforceable, then the entirety of this arbitration provision shall be null and void.
F. Notwithstanding any provision in these Terms of Use to the contrary, we agree that if Edvisors makes any material change to this Section 19 (other than a change to the Edvisors Notice Address), you may reject any such change by sending us written notice, to the Edvisors Notice Address, within 30 days of the change. By rejecting any future change, you are agreeing that you will arbitrate any dispute between us in accordance with the language of these Terms of Use in the form prior to such rejected change.
20. Compliance with FTC Guidelines on Endorsements/Testimonials
If you choose to promote our services to the public, including your own personal social networks, you agree that you will comply with the FTC's Guidelines Concerning the Use of Testimonials and Endorsements in Advertising ("Guidelines").
21. Jurisdiction
These Terms of Use and any dispute of any kind that arises with Edvisors shall be governed by the laws of the State of Nevada without regard to the principles of conflicts of laws. You further agree to irrevocably submit to the exclusive personal jurisdiction of the state and federal courts sitting in Clark County, Nevada.
22. Entire Agreement
These Terms of Use together with any other terms and conditions or policies that incorporate these Terms of Use by reference, constitutes the complete, final and exclusive understanding between Edvisors and you relating to the subject matter hereof and governs your use of the Service(s), superseding all prior or contemporaneous understandings, agreements and/or communications with respect to such subject matter. You may be subject to additional terms and conditions that may apply when you obtain or use third-party content, third-party software or goods and services provided by or through Clients, Sponsors, Reward Partners, Affiliates or other third-parties.
23. Assignment
These Terms of Use, and any rights and licenses granted hereunder, may not be transferred or assigned by you, but may be assigned by Edvisors without restriction.
24. Invalidity; Waiver
If any provision of these Terms of Use is deemed invalid by a court of competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of these Terms of Use, which shall remain in full force and effect. It is the parties’ intention that the court modify such invalid provision to give it the fullest effect permissible under applicable law. No waiver of any term of these Terms of Use shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or any other term, and Edvisors’ failure to assert any right or provision under these Terms of Use shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision.
25. Termination
A Member may terminate their membership in any of the Registered Services with or without cause at any time. A Member’s termination of Registered Services is effective upon Member’s terminating his/her membership on the Service’s Website. A visitor to any Edvisors Website who is not a Member but who does not agree to any of the terms and conditions of these Terms of Use should not use any of the Services and should exit the Website immediately.
Edvisors may terminate membership and use of any of the Registered Services and may remove User Submissions in its sole discretion, effective immediately and without prior notice, for any reason, including, without limitation, failure to provide accurate Registration Data; lack of use; or if Edvisors believes that Member or has violated or acted inconsistently with the letter or spirit of these Terms of Use.
Upon termination by either you or Edvisors: (i) Edvisors may immediately deactivate or delete your account and all related information and files and/or bar any further access to such files or the Services: (ii) your rights to use the Service(s) ceases immediately, including any rights to contests, games, or activities active at the time of termination; (iii) should you object to any of these Terms of Use or any subsequent modifications thereto or become dissatisfied with the Service, your only recourse is to immediately discontinue use of the Service. You agree that Edvisors shall not be liable to you or to any third-party for any termination of your account or your access to the Services.
26. Definitions
A. Sponsor: Any company or an organization that pays Edvisors to plan and carries out a sweepstakes, contest or activity on an Edvisors’ owned and operated website or mail-in promotion.
B. Client: Any company which Edvisors has a contract with to connect Edvisors members with. The Client would plan and carry out the sweepstakes, survey, contest or activity on Client’s owned and operated website or mail-in promotion.
C. Partner: Any company or organization who takes part in an undertaking with Edvisors, with shared risks and profits. For example, the Partner may own and operate a website where a survey occurs, but Edvisors would be operating the correlating sweepstakes where “Points” earned by through Partner’s survey, would be redeemed.
D. Affiliate: Affiliate is any business under common ownership or control.
27. User Suggestions
You acknowledge and agree that any questions, comments, suggestions, ideas, feedback or other information provided by you to Edvisors are not commercial and you grant us a worldwide, royalty-free license to distribute, publish, modify, edit or otherwise use your submissions. Edvisors shall be entitled to the unrestricted use and dissemination of these submissions for any purpose, commercial or otherwise without any acknowledgement of or compensation to you.
28. Questions/Comments
If you have any questions or comments about the Services or become aware of misuse of the Services by any person, please contact us at info@edvisors.com or at the following address: Edvisors Network, Inc., 10000 W. Charleston Blvd., Suite 200, Las Vegas, NV 89135
Privacy Policy
Last Updated: June 30, 2020
Edvisors Network, Inc. (“Edvisors”) publishes several different websites, including, but not limited to the following:
Edvisors.com
ScholarshipPoints.com
StudentScholarshipSearch.com
PrivateStudentLoans.com
StudentLoanConsolidator.com
HowToGetIn.com
CollegeToolkit.com
FinancialAidForum.com
RewardFish.com
Table of Contents:
Information We Collect
How We Collect Information
How We Use Your Information
How We Share Your Information
Children's Privacy
How We Protect Your Information
Links to Other Sites
How to Update Your Information
Friend Referrals
Your Rights with Regard to Our Collection Practices
Changing Our Privacy Policy
Retention
Disputes: No Rights of Third Parties
Questions Regarding Our Privacy Practices
This Privacy Policy applies to all our websites (collectively, “Site”) and Services owned and operated by Edvisors. The term "Services," means any services, transactions, or other engagements you might have with Edvisors.
Please carefully read this Privacy Policy, which is part of our Terms of Use, before using our Site and/or Services. If you do not agree with the Terms of Use and/or this Privacy Policy, you must refrain from using our Site and/or Services. By accessing or using our Site and/or Services you agree to our use of your information consistent with the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy.
Questions Regarding Our Privacy Practices
If you still have questions after reading our Privacy Policy, here are a few ways you can contact us:
Edvisors
Attn: Customer Service
10000 W. Charleston Blvd., Suite 200
Las Vegas, NV 89135 USA
You may also reach us during regular business hours at:
(888) 972-1010
1. Information We Collect
Category
Examples Provided
Information We Have Collected and may Collect As You Use Our Websites and Our Services
Identifiers
Personal identifiers may include, without limitation, name, signature, social security number, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, passport number, driver’s license or state identification card number, insurance policy number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information.
Name, email address, IP address, and User ID, cell phone number, account username.
Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e)).
A name, signature, Social Security number, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, passport number, driver's license or state identification card number, insurance policy number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information. Some Personal Information included in this category may overlap with other categories.
Household income range, student assets, federal or private student loan debt, credit score range, student loan amount sought.
Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law.
Information Related to Characteristics Protected Under California or Federal Law such as gender, age, marital status, and citizenship.
Gender, age 40 years plus, marital status, religion, citizenship, military or veteran status, disability, ethnicity.
Commercial information.
Records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies
Preferred school size, preferred residence, sweepstakes participation records, ScholarshipPoints activities, reward activities, e-gift cards information, survey responses.
Internet or other similar network activity.
Browsing history, search history, information on a consumer's interaction with a website, application, or advertisement.
Data and time of interaction with an advertisement, advertisement ID, website ID, session ID, browsing history, search history, chat transcript.
Sensory data.
Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information.
Call recording when you contact our call center, photos.
Professional or employment-related information.
Current or past job history or performance evaluations.
Job information and status, job title.
Non-public education information (per the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (20 U.S.C. Section 1232g, 34 C.F.R. Part 99)).
Education records directly related to a student maintained by an educational institution or party acting on its behalf, such as grades, transcripts, class lists, student schedules, student identification codes, student financial information, or student disciplinary records.
School name, school address, GPA, exam scores, major, degree, graduation date, class rank, grade levels.
Inferences drawn from other Personal Information.
Profile reflecting a person's preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes.
Propensity to select certain offers, scholarships, advertisements, content, colleges, and/or universities that may interest you, and gender.
2. How We Collect Information
A. Information You Provide
We may collect personally identifiable information you provide to us:
When you fill out forms or fields through our Services;
When you sign up for any newsletters or other materials through our Services;
When you provide information to us through a third-party application, service or web site;
When you communicate with us or request information about us or our Services, whether via email or other means;
When you participate in online surveys hosted by us or our third-party partners;
When you participate in any of our marketing initiatives, including, contests, sweepstakes, or other promotions;
When you participate in forums, chats or provide user generated content or submissions; and
Usage, viewing and technical data, including your device identifier or IP address, when you visit our sites, use our applications on third-party sites or platforms or open emails we send.
We may also collect different types of information about your location, including general information (e.g., IP address, zip code) and more specific information (e.g., GPS-based information from mobile devices used to access the Services), and may use that information to customize the Services with location-based information, advertising, and features. This information may be shared with our service providers, vendors or advertisers.
B. Information Third Parties Provide
We also may collect information about you from sources other than from you directly, such as from social media websites (Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter or others), other users and our business partners.
This Privacy Policy applies solely to our privacy practices. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third parties, even if our ads contain links to third party websites and even if we have an independent business relationship with that third party. This policy does not address, and we are not responsible for information practices (including collection, usage, disclosure or data security) of any third parties, including any third party operating any site or service to which our web site links. The inclusion of a link on our Site does not imply our or our affiliates’ endorsement of the linked site or service.
We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy of each and every web site that you visit to be sure you understand the terms and conditions that apply to you from each of them.
Supplementation of Personal Information: In order to provide certain services to you, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submitted to us with information from third party sources. For example:
Address Verification: If you provide your email address during member registration or otherwise, we use third parties in order to verify your email address information registration process.
Enhancement of Profile Information: We obtain marketing data from third parties and add it to our existing user database, to better target our advertising and to provide pertinent offers for which we think you would be interested. To enrich our profiles of individual customers, we tie this information to the personal Information you submitted to us. If you choose to link any of your social media accounts to your account, you may be given the option to log into your account using the credentials from any such social media accounts. When you choose to use this log-in feature, we may obtain information from all of the social media accounts that you have chosen to link to your account. Such information may include, for example, your name, date of birth, gender, location, profile photo, interests, activities, likes, check-ins, languages, e-mail address, mailing address, telephone number, professional information, contacts or similar information. You may unlink any of your social media accounts from your account by modifying your account settings. When you do so, we will stop obtaining new information from such social media accounts.
When We Advertise on Third Party Sites: When you visit a site on which we advertise and click through our advertisement, we may place cookies on your computer or use pixel tags. The information that we collect through this technology is not personally identifiable.
C. Information Collected Through Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
We use tracking technologies to help provide content, to measure promotional effectiveness, to offer advertisements and/or other offerings, to recognize you and your preferences when you return to our site, to help us learn more about how our users use our sites, to personalize your experience, to assess which areas of our site you visit, and to remarket to you after you leave our site.
Third Party Tracking: We permit third parties that we have agreements with us to track you when you are on our web site. When you leave our web site there is a chance that these third parties may continue to track you.
A few tracking technologies include, without limitation, images, scripts and subsequent technology and methods later developed:
Cookies: Edvisors uses “cookies” and other technologies to help us learn more about how our users use our sites and to recognize you when you return. “Cookies” (which may be html files, Flash files or other technology) are text files that are stored on your browser or device by websites, apps, online media, and advertisements that can be used to help recognize you as an Edvisors user and help store your preferences and activity. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies may store user preferences and other information, and can be deleted or blocked by changing the settings on your web browser. You may also be able to modify your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis. However, choosing to decline cookies may hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on Edvisors Site.
Web Beacons: Web beacons are small graphic images or other web programming which may be included in our services. Web beacons can be invisible to you and are used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to our Sites, to monitor how users navigate our Sites, to count how many e-mails that were sent were actually opened or to count how many specific articles or links were actually viewed.
HTML5 and Locally Stored Objects: Similar to cookies are “locally stored objects” which we may also use for storing analytics information. Locally stored objects, such as HTML5 Web Storage, are used for similar purposes as cookies but typically may contain a greater amount and different types of data than browser cookies. Most current versions of common web browsers clear this locally stored data when you delete or clear your cookie cache. To confirm whether this is the case for the browser you are using, or to learn more about how to precisely control this data storage, please consult the Help function of your browser.
Analytics Tools and Third Party Cookies: Edvisors uses temporary cookies to help us determine how people travel through our site. A temporary cookie expires when you close your browser. This web site also uses third-party analytics tools (such as Google Analytics) to collect information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use this information only to improve this site. Such tools use permanent cookies to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, and the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Edvisors. Third-parties providing such analytics tools may also transfer this information to other third-parties where required to do so by law, or where such third-parties process the information on their behalf. The third-party analytics provider cannot associate your IP address with your personally identifiable information. By using this web site, you consent to the processing of data about you by a third-party click tracking analytics provider in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
For some of our products, we use Google Analytics Advertising Features, including Remarketing with Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, DoubleClick Platform integrations, and Google Analytics Demographic and Interest Reporting.
These features use first party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) for connecting the tracking activity performed by Google Analytics and its cookies with the Adwords advertising network and the DoubleClick cookie (a third party cookie). The use of these cookies allows us to optimize the delivery of ad content specifically targeted to a visitor’s interests based upon previous visits to our site.
You may opt out of the Google Analytics service with Google’s Browser Add-on that’s available at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.
For information in general about Google’s remarketing ad campaigns, and specifically about information regarding DoubleClick cookies and how to control and manage Google’s advertising cookies for these campaigns, visit https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/.
For another Google resource for opting out of Google’s use of cookies, visit https://www.google.com/settings/ads/.
For another resource recommended by Google for opting out of a third party vendor’s use of cookies, visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
You can exercise cookie choices by visiting http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.
Our web site may also use, on some pages, the HotJar Analysis and Feedback tool. The HotJar service helps us analyze how visitors use our Site. It reveals the online behavior and feedback of our web site's visitors. By combining both A) Analysis and B) Feedback tools, Hotjar gives us the 'big picture' of how to improve our web site visitor’s experience and the site’s performance. We do not collect through the HotJar service or transfer to HotJar any personally identifiable information. We only use the HotJar service to record, for some visitors on some websites and on a completely anonymous basis, information such as mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity as well as non-personally identifiable information text you type in some of our Site. Information about the browser (type, version, screen size, etc.), basic information about the user (IP address, language, time zone) and data containing mouse movements, clicks, and scroll events are sent to HotJar.
For more information see HotJar's Privacy Policy at https://www.hotjar.com/privacy.
You can choose to disable the HotJar service at https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out.
Online Advertising Networks and Third Party Cookies: Edvisors sometimes runs online ad campaigns that display Edvisors ads to you based on your likely interests. We may learn your likely interests when you use our Site and from other companies and websites that help us understand your likely interests. These types of ads are often called “interest-based ads” or “online behavioral advertising.” We hire “ad networks” to display these ads on websites across the Internet. Edvisors adheres to the DAA’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising.
The ad networks we hire to display these ads set their own cookies on your browser and use web beacons to measure the effectiveness of these ads and to understand your likely interests. Our ad networks and Edvisors both learn which Edvisors ads are shown to you, which ads are clicked on, and on which web page the ads were displayed.
Third-party companies may use non-cookie technologies to recognize your computer or device and/or to collect and record information about your web surfing activity including your activities on this web site. These technologies may be used directly on this web site. Please keep in mind that your web browser may not permit you to block the use of these non-cookie technologies, and those browser settings that block cookies may have no effect on such techniques.
Notwithstanding the above, we may share information collected from you with third party data providers including web log data and/or hashed email addresses. Third party data providers may place anonymous cookies on your browser to receive customized ads or content, which you can opt out of at http://www.aboutads.info/choices.
For more general information about interest-based ads and your choices, visit the Digital Advertising Alliance at http://www.aboutads.info/choices.
Cross-device and cross-app technology: We use the term “devices” to refer collectively to computers and mobile devices, as well as the internet browsers and other applications on your devices that interact with the internet. We and our customers may use technology that establishes deterministic or statistical connections among related devices (such as smartphones, tablets, and computers) to deliver more relevant advertising to you and for advertising analytics and reporting purposes. This includes cross device data collection which refers to the process of collecting data from separate devices that have been determined through statistical analysis to be linked or related.
D How We Respond to Browser “Do Not Track” Signals
Some web browsers or mobile device operating systems incorporate a “Do Not Track” (a/k/a DNT) feature that signals to websites that you visit that you do not want to have your online activity tracked. We do not respond to web browser and/or mobile device operating systems “Do Not Track” signals at this time.
3. How We Use Your Information
In addition to the uses described in the Information We Collect section of this Privacy Policy, we use your information to provide you the services you request (such as promotions, lending and scholarship information), to customize our sites, to improve your user experience and our services, and to provide information about other products and services which we think might interest you.
To provide you with and target advertising based on your activity and interests, both on our own Sites and applications and on third-party sites, platforms and applications.
In addition, we use your information to operate, administer, test and improve our sites, and to customize and improve the user experience. We may also use your information for our general business purposes such as analytics, market research and financial reporting.
4. How We Share and Sell Your Information
Edvisors Sites: All Edvisors’ sites have access to and use information about you for the purposes described above.
Advertisers and Marketing Partners: We may share your information with and/or sell your information to third parties whose products and services we think may be of interest to you, such as educational institutions; financial companies, such as those that make or arrange student loans and other financial products; non-financial institutions, such as retailers who sell a wide range of products and services to consumers; direct marketing companies; or nonprofit organizations. These third parties may be domestic or international.
Third Party Market Research (MR) Companies: We may also share or sell your personal information and/or social-demographic information, including, without limitation, a unique identification number (“UID”), postal code, gender, marital status, education, ethnicity/race (where permitted by applicable law), employment related information, and non-personally identifiable information on household members, with third party sample/market research companies (individually each a “Third Party MR Company” and collectively the “Third Party MR Companies”) for the purpose of identifying survey opportunities that you may be eligible for through the Third Party MR Companies. If you are eligible for a survey opportunity, the Third Party MR Company will provide your unique identification number and a survey link to us and we will invite you to participate in the survey. We will share your name, email address, or phone number with the Third Party MR Companies. In connection with the sharing of your information with a Third Party MR Company, your information may be transferred and stored outside of your country of residence, including, without limitation, in the United States. If you have any questions about this data sharing, you may reach us during regular business hours at (888) 972-1010. Your participation in such survey opportunities does not entitle you to any benefits offered by, or membership with, the Third Party MR Companies.
Analytics Partners: We may share or sell your information with third parties who use the information solely for analytical purposes. We make certain anonymized or aggregated information (which is information that does not personally identify you) available to third parties, to: (a) comply with various reporting obligations; (b) for business or marketing purposes; or (c) to assist such parties in understanding our users’ interests, habits, and usage patterns for certain programs, content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality available through the Service.
Third-Party Service Providers: From time to time we may use third parties to perform specific services, such as sending emails or newsletters to Edvisors users. If we use a third party to provide specific services, then information (such as contact information) may be shared with that party to the extent necessary for the third party to provide these services. These third-party service providers are only allowed to use personally identifiable information for the purpose of providing the specific services requested by Edvisors. The third-party services covered by this paragraph do not include links to third-party sites found on our sites.
Examples of service providers include:
Fulfillment and account servicing vendors, which help us provide products, services and information to you, service your account or benefits, and perform payment processing services;
Marketing and communications vendors, which help us market our products/services to you, conduct promotions, surveys and other outreach campaigns;
Research and development vendors, which help us develop and improve our products and services;
Data and business analytics vendors, which help us collect, analyze and improve the accuracy of our data (including Personal Information);
IT and network administration vendors, which provide services such as data storage and management, website hosting, and data security;
Professional service firms, which provide accounting, legal, and other professional services; and
General service providers, which help us with day-to-day business operations such as office support services, courier services, facilities management, and document destruction.
Disclosure to Law Enforcement and Similar Disclosures: While Edvisors strives to protect the personal information of all users, Edvisors will disclose information if legally required to do so, if requested to do so by a government entity, or if it believes in good faith that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect our rights or property or our affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public.
As Part of a Business Transfer: We may share your information, including your personal information, and usage information with any parent, subsidiary or affiliate entity for the purposes disclosed in this Privacy Policy. We also reserve the right to disclose and transfer some or all such information: (i) to a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of Edvisors; or (ii) in connection with any merger, acquisition, consolidation, restructuring, bankruptcy, sale of assets or other corporate change involving us and/or our affiliates. We may transfer the corresponding information regarding our customers and users of the Services, including personal information, to third parties evaluating or facilitating the transaction.
Nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to interfere with our ability to transfer all or part of our business, equity interests, or assets (including the services) to an affiliate or non-affiliated third party at any time, for any purpose, without any limitation, and without notice or any compensation to you.
Promotions: We may share your information in connection with any promotion you enter on or through the Site or Services, as necessary to administer, market, sponsor, or fulfill the promotion or as required by applicable laws, rules or regulations (for example, to provide winners’ lists or make required filings as appropriate) or in accordance with the applicable Official Rules of the promotion/sweepstakes you enter.
Social Media Features: Our web site may include Social Media features, such as the Facebook “Like” button. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our web site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the Privacy Policy of the company providing them.
Offer Walls: Our Site may display third-party advertisers’ offers. These advertisers may in turn display their own offers. These offers are not controlled by or made by Edvisors. These offers may be displayed to you based on certain technical information, such as your geographic area or other anonymous demographic information. After clicking on one of these offers, you may no longer be on a site hosted by Edvisors or a partnering Third Party Platform. Edvisors may provide points or other virtual rewards to users in exchange for interaction with an advertisement or completion of a specific activity in furtherance of the advertiser’s promotion. Such activities may include signing up for an account with the advertiser. To properly credit user accounts and to prevent fraud, a unique identifier and anonymous demographic information may be shared with the offer provider. This information is used to ensure proper crediting of your account, prevent fraud or duplicate offers and to resolve any customer service inquiries that may arise. Once you complete an offer, you may then be returned to an Edvisors website or service.
Consent: In addition to the other sharing practices described in this Privacy Policy, we may also share your information with third parties with your consent.
5. Children's Policy
This web site is not directed or otherwise promoted for use by children under the age of thirteen (13). Edvisors does not knowingly collect, maintain or use personal information from our web sites or Services about children under age thirteen. If a child whom we know to be under age thirteen sends personal information to us online, we will only use that information to respond directly to that child, notify parents or seek parental consent, and will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. We are not, however, responsible for the collection and use of information by companies or individuals unaffiliated with us whose web sites may contain links to ours. Because we do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen, we also do not knowingly distribute such information to third parties. We do not knowingly allow children under the age of thirteen to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information via our site.
6. How We Protect Your Information
We take the security of your personal information very seriously. Edvisors maintains certain physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to help protect our data. We require all third-party advertising and marketing partners with whom we share your personally identifiable information to make reasonable efforts to protect your information, however we "do not guarantee" the security of personal information sold to or shared with third parties.
We cannot, however, ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us or store on the Services and you do so at your own risk. We also cannot guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, electronic, or administrative safeguards.
7. Links to Other Sites
This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Edvisors does not exercise control over the information, products, services or policies of third-party companies linked from or accessible through our site. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each and every third party site so you can understand how they collect, use, and share your information.
8. How to Update Your Information
We endeavor to ensure that personal information is as accurate, complete and current as necessary for the purposes for which we use that information. We encourage you to visit your account, if applicable, to review your personal information.
The appropriate method(s) for accessing your information, if any, will depend on which of our Site and Services you have either visited or used. Depending on the web site and Service, you may have the ability to view or edit some of your information online, by logging into the Services and visiting your account profile page. You may also reach us during regular business hours at (888) 972-1010 to request access to, correct, or delete any personal information that you have provided to us; however, we may ask you to verify your identity and provide other details to help us to respond to your request. We may not provide you with access to or the ability to modify certain portions of your information as we deem necessary for security, legal, regulatory or business purposes.
9. Friend Referrals
We may provide you with an opportunity to invite and inform your friends, family and acquaintances (“Friends”) about our services.
If you elect to use our referral feature, we will automatically send to your Friend, to the email address you provided, one or more emails or other communications, on your behalf, inviting them to visit or register for the Edvisors’ Site and Services. You warrant and represent that you have your Friend’s consent to provide us with his or her information for this purpose, and that you will not give us referral information for any person not permitted to use the Edvisors’ Site and Services, including, without limitation a child under the age of 13, a person whose account has previously been suspended or deactivated, or a person residing or located in a territory where use of the Edvisors’ Site and Services are not authorized.
10. Your Rights with Regards to Our Collection Practices
Unsubscribe from Our E-mails: If you do not wish to receive promotional e-mails from us, whether on our behalf or on behalf of a client, including our e-newsletters, follow the unsubscribe process at the bottom of the promotional e-mail. Alternatively, you can unsubscribe here. Note that even if you unsubscribe, you may still receive transactional e-mails from us (e.g., e-mails related to the completion of your registration, correction of user data, password reset requests, reminder e-mails that you have requested, and any other similar communications essential to your transactions on or made through the services). It may take up to 10 days to process your opt out request.
Opting Out — Advertisers and Third Parties: If you opt out, we will stop sharing and/or selling your personal information in Edvisors’ proprietary database to help third parties (including Third Party Market Research (MR) Companies) or marketing partners send or tailor ads and content to you, including through email, direct mail or online display marketing. Doing so will not opt you out of our marketing partners’ or third parties’ databases, only data in Edvisors’ own database – so other companies that we work with may still send ads, offers and content to you. To opt out of Edvisors sharing and/or selling your information with third parties and/or marketing partners for their marketing purposes, opt out here.
Opting Out of Interest Based Advertising: If you wish to opt out of the use of your technical information by online advertising networks, please visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices. You can also disable or delete cookies directly on your web browser. Please see your browser’s “help” content for information on how to do this.
You can opt out of our use of your online viewing behavior data to serve you interest-based advertising on third-party sites at www.aboutads.info or by clicking on the Interest-based Ads link in the footer of our Site and navigating to the consumer opt-out page. Use the same links to opt out of interest-based advertising on our services from any third-party advertising networks we may use.
If you would like to opt out of having interest-based ad targeting, click here.
Your access to our Site should not be affected if you do not accept cookies served by third parties.
If you have any problems or questions regarding your privacy preferences or opt out options, you may reach us during regular business hours at (888) 972-1010.
California Residents
Your Rights and Choices
The California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) provides consumers (California residents) with specific rights regarding their personal information. Beginning on January 1, 2020, California Civil Code Section 1798.100 permits consumers who are California residents: 1) The right to know what personal information is being collected about them; 2) The right to know whether their personal information is sold or disclosed and to whom; 3) The right to Opt-Out of the sale of personal information; 4) The right to access their personal information; 5) The right to equal service and price, even if they exercise their privacy rights
This section describes your CCPA rights and explains how to exercise those rights.
Right to Request Opt Out of the Sale of Personal information
A California consumer has a right, at any time, to opt out of the sale of their Personal Information by a business to third parties. As mentioned above, we do sell personal information.
We do not sell the personal information of consumers we actually know are less than 16 years of age.
To exercise the right to opt out, you or (your authorized representative) can provide the request by visiting the following webpage or contact us via chat, email or telephone. The webpage can also be accessed by clicking on the Do Not Sell My Personal Information link at the bottom of our webpages.
Any information you submit to exercise your opt out right, will be used solely for processing your opt out request.
Disclosure and Access Right
You have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information over the past 12 months. Only you, or a person that you authorize in writing to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request or a request made on your behalf, we will disclose to you:
The categories of personal information we collected about you.
The categories of sources for the personal information we collected about you.
Our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that personal information.
The categories of third parties with whom we share that personal information.
The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you (also called a data portability request).
If we disclosed your personal information for a business purpose, we will identify the personal information categories that each category of recipient obtained.
Our verification process will take into consideration the type and sensitivity of information requested, and any risk of harm posed by any unauthorized access or deletion. Thus, we will either verify your identity to a reasonably high degree of certainty or a reasonable degree of certainty. Re-authentication is needed before disclosing information by having a confirmation email sent to you. This confirmation email requires you to click the link before a request will be approved.
How to Make a Disclosure Request
Such requests will only be fulfilled upon the receipt of verifiable request. To exercise your right to make such a request, please use one of the methods below.
Calling us at (888) 972-1010
Chat
Emailing us at: info@edvisors.com
Deletion Right
You have the right to request that we delete any of your personal information that we collected from you and maintained, subject to certain exceptions. Only you, or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request), we will delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your personal information from our records, unless an exception applies.
We will require you to provide information including, but not limited to the following: name, email address, and date of birth to reasonably verify your identity. We will attempt to match the information you provided with the information in our records. Re-authentication is needed before deleting personal information by having a confirmation email sent to you. This confirmation email requires you to click the button before a request will be approved.
We will not be able to process the request until we have verified your identity.
We may rightfully retain your personal information if it is collected:
To complete transactions for goods or services, perform contracts, or for anticipated ongoing relationships;
For the detection of protection from illegal activity or to assist prosecution;
To identify or repair errors;
For free speech or other rights provided by law;
For compliance with California Electronics Communications Privacy Act;
For the engagement in statistical research in the public interest with consumer informed consent;
For internal uses based on consumer’s relationship with the business;
For legal obligation compliance;
For otherwise internal uses in a legal matter in context with the reason that consumer provided the information;
For any other purposes as authorized by the California Consumer Privacy Act.
How to Make a Deletion Request
Such requests will only be fulfilled upon the receipt of verifiable request.
To exercise your right to make such a request, please use one of the methods below.
Calling us at (888) 972-1010
Deletion Request Form
Emailing us at: customerservice@edvisors.com
Chat
Authorized Agent / Representative
If you are an authorized agent submitting a request for another California resident, Under the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), a California consumer may use an authorized agent to make a CCPA privacy request on the consumer’s behalf. To make a request on behalf of a California consumer, please submit your request through one of the provided submission methods and designate whether you are exercising a request as an authorized agent. We will verify the authorized agent’s authority with the consumer.
We may require the authorized agent to provide a copy of either (a) a letter signed by the customer authorizing the agent to submit a CCPA request on his or her behalf, or (b) a valid power of attorney issued pursuant to California Probate Code sections 4000 to 4465 and include a phone number where the agent may be reached (along with proof of your identity).
Right to Non-Discrimination
We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights. Unless permitted by the CCPA, we will not:
Deny you goods or services.
Charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties.
Provide you a different level or quality of goods or services.
Suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.
Your California Privacy Rights: A Notice to California Users (California Civil Code Section 1798.83)
California's "Shine the Light" law, Civil Code section 1798.83, requires certain businesses to respond to requests from California residents asking about the business' practices related to disclosing personal information to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. Alternately, businesses may have in place a policy not to disclose personal information of California residents to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes if the California resident has exercised an option to opt out of such information-sharing. We have such a policy in place.
Any California residents who have an established relationship with Edvisors may opt out of Edvisors disclosing your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Under California law, third parties include affiliates of Edvisors. If you do not want Edvisors to disclose your personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes you can opt out here.
Pursuant to California privacy law, registered users under 18 years of age may request to have content or information posted by the user removed from any of our online platforms. In order to effectuate removal of such content or information, you may reach us during regular business hours at (888) 972-1010.
The removal of content does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information posted on any of our online platforms by the registered user.
We do not advertise or market any of the products or services identified in Chapter 22.1 Sec. 22580 (i) to users we have actual knowledge are under 18 years of age.
11. Changing Our Privacy Policy
Your use of any web site owned or operated by Edvisors indicates an acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy. Edvisors reserves the right to update or amend this Privacy Policy at any time to reflect our current privacy practices. Changes are effective upon posting of the revised Privacy Policy to the web site. If Edvisors decides to materially change this Privacy Policy, we may provide additional notice of the change such as through a prominent notice on the web site or by sending an email to registered users.
12. Retention
We retain your Personal Information for as long as we have a relationship with you. We also retain your Personal Information for a period of time after our relationship with you has ended where there is an ongoing business need to retain it. This includes retention to comply with our legal, regulatory, tax, and/or accounting obligations. Generally, we retain Personal Information for approximately two (2) years after our relationship with you has ended, but the term for which we retain your Personal Information may be longer or shorter. We do so in accordance with our data retention policies and applicable law.
13. Disputes; No Rights of Third Parties
If you choose to access our Site or use any of our services, any dispute over privacy is subject to our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the laws of the United States and the State of Nevada. This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties.
If you have a disability that prevents or limits your ability to access this Notice, our Customer Service team will make efforts to provide you with an accessible version.
14. Questions Regarding Our Privacy Practices
If you still have questions, here are a few ways you can contact us:
Phone
(888) 972-1010
Email customerservice@edvisors.com
Address
Edvisors Network, Inc.
Attn: Customer Service
10000 West Charleston Blvd.
Suite 200
Las Vegas, Nevada 89135
Disclaimer
The information contained on this web site is provided for general informational and educational purposes and is not, nor intended to be, legal, financial or tax advice. The publisher is not authorized to practice in front of the IRS and is not subject to IRS Circular 230. This information is general in nature and may not apply to the specific circumstances of individual readers. No claims are made about the accuracy, timeliness or usefulness of the content contained on this web site or any site linked to this site. Users of this site should seek specific guidance directly from a qualified legal, financial or tax professional. Nothing contained on or provided through this site is intended to be or is to be used as a substitute for professional advice.
Copyright © 2020 by Edvisors.com. All rights reserved.
×
Get My School Snapshot
Provide your email address below for immediate access to the downloaded PDF of this page. We will also email the PDF to your inbox.
Thank you. Your download should begin immediately. A PDF of this page has also been sent to the email provided.
Email School PDF Form
Email Address
Agree to Terms
By clicking "Download Now" I agree to the Edvisors Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. We strongly encourage you to read our privacy policy to understand how we use and share your information.
Download Now
